arcadiapower.com 2017-01-26

# Privacy Policy | Arcadia Power

## The Arcadia Power Privacy Policy

Effective Date: 6.1.2014

## Table of Contents

Personal Information   
Information We Collect   
Use of Information   
Sharing of Information   
Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Internet Technologies   
Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms   
Third Parties That Provide Content or Functionality on Our Services   
Consent to International Transfer of Data   
Collection of Information From Children   
Your Choices & Access to Your Information   
Your California Privacy Rights   
Information Security   
How to Contact Us   
Changes to This Privacy Policy in the Future

Arcadia Power, Inc. and our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Arcadia Power”) recognize that when you choose to provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to treat it responsibly.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and disclose information that we collect about you, including through Arcadia Power’s websites, mobile applications, and other online services or social media platforms that refer or link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Sites”), and how we protect the security of your Personal Information.

It is important that you read the Privacy Policy carefully because anytime you use our Sites, you consent to the practices we describe in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the practices described in the Privacy Policy, you should not use our Sites.

## Personal Information

As used herein, Personal Information means information, or a combination of pieces of information, that could reasonably allow you to be identified such as a name, address, telephone number, mobile number, email address, utility account number and password, bank account number, or credit card number. Personal Information does not include “aggregate” information, which is data we collect about the use of our Sites or about a group or category of services or users, from which individual identities or other personal information has been removed. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our collection and use of aggregate information.

## Information We Collect

We may collect information about you and, if applicable, the computer or device you use to access our Sites in a variety of ways:

You may provide us information directly   
We may collect information about you when you use our Sites or view our online advertisements   
We may collect additional information about you in accordance with applicable law 

Our Sites may link to third-party websites and services that are outside our control. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information collected by such third-parties. You should exercise caution, and review the privacy statements applicable to such third parties.

## Information you provide us directly

We will collect any Personal Information that you provide when you create an account with Arcadia Power and that you choose to enter through our Sites. The following are examples of Personal Information you may provide us directly:

  * Name
  * E-mail address, physical address and/or zip code, and phone number
  * Utility account username and password
  * Credit card number, bank account number, or other payment information

You may also provide other information such as demographic information and product interests when you create an account, complete a survey, connect through a social feed, or send us an email or message.

## Information we collect when you use our online Sites or view our online advertisements

We use standard Internet technologies, such as cookies, web beacons, and local stored objects, to collect information about your computer or device and your online activity. The following are examples of the types of information that we may collect with these technologies:

  * Your browser type and operating system
  * IP address and/or device ID
  * Your browsing behavior on our Sites, such as the amount of time spent viewing our online Sites and the links you click within our online and mobile Sites
  * Websites you visit before or after our Sites
  * Arcadia Power e-mails you open and/or forward
  * Arcadia Power offers or links you connect to via e-mails

If you use a mobile device to access our Sites, we may collect information about that device, such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile telephone number, or a device identifier, as well as the date, time, and content of your messages relevant to your use of our mobile services.

## Additional information we may collect about you

We collect information you allow a third party to provide to us such as your monthly utility usage. In addition, we may also receive information about you from publicly and commercially available sources.

We also may collect other information about you, your device, or your use of our Sites in ways that we describe to you at the point of collection or otherwise with your consent.

All of the information we collect about you may be combined to help us enhance and improve our Sites and tailor our communications to you.

## Use of Information

We use information collected through our Sites, for the purposes described in this Policy or elsewhere on our Sites. For example, we may use your information we collect:

  * to provide you with services, products, or other information you request, and to process and complete such requests and any related transactions;
  * to send you confirmations, updates, alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, our Sites;
  * to notify you about important changes to our Sites and services;
  * to customize your experience with our Sites, including by providing you with relevant advertising on our websites and elsewhere;
  * to send you newsletters and otherwise provide you with information or services you request or that we think will be of interest of you, such as information to keep you informed about various issues, events, resources, promotions, discounts, products, and services;
  * to manage and improve our Sites and offerings, including analyzing the use of our Sites and determining the effectiveness of our advertising;
  * to request feedback and to otherwise contact you about your use of our Sites;
  * to respond to your e-mails, submissions, questions, comments, and requests, and to provide customer services;
  * to protect the security and integrity of our Sites;
  * to enforce our legal rights; and
  * otherwise with your consent.

## Sharing of Information

We may share your Personal Information only in the following circumstances:

  * **Affiliates.** We may share Personal Information within Arcadia Power among our various subsidiaries and affiliates. 
  * **Service Providers.** We rely on third-party service providers to perform a variety of services on our behalf. To do so, we may need to share your Personal Information with them. 
  * **Other Parties When Required by Law or as Necessary to Protect Our Sites.** There may be instances when we disclose your Personal Information to other parties: 
    * To comply with the law or respond to legal process or a request for cooperation by a government entity
    * To prevent fraud or verify and enforce compliance with the policies governing our Sites
    * Where permitted by law, to protect the rights, property, or safety of Arcadia Power, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers or employees
  * **Other Parties In Connection With A Corporate Transaction.** We may disclose your Personal Information to a third party in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of a business or our assets to a third party, such as in connection with a merger or in the event of a bankruptcy reorganization or liquidation. 
  * Other Parties With Your Consent At Your Direction. In addition to the disclosures described in this Privacy Policy, we may share Personal Information about you with third parties when you consent to or request such sharing. For example, in order to fulfill enrollment in our services, we must share your Personal Information with your local utility company. We also may share your Personal Information with third parties that provide products or services that may be of interest to you and you may opt-out of the sharing of this information.
  * Aggregated and Non-Personal Information. We also may share data that is not reasonably linkable to a particular consumer or device (for example, information that has been aggregated with other records) for general business purposes. We may also share aggregated or anonymized information, which may be shared with third parties without your consent. For example, we may share your aggregated and anonymous information to publish trends about energy use and conservation and help utility companies provide demand-response services.

## Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Internet Technologies

We, as well as certain third parties that provide content, advertising, and other functionality on our Sites, may use cookies, web beacons and other similar technologies in certain areas of our online Sites. Click here for more information about cookies, web beacons and other Internet technologies.

## Do-Not-Track Signals and Similar Mechanisms

Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites and other online services with which a user communications. There is no industry standard that governs what, if anything, websites should do when they receive these signals. Arcadia Power currently does not take action in response to these signals. If and when a standard is established and accepted, Arcadia Power may revisit its policy on responding to these signals.

## Third Parties That Provide Content or Functionality on Our Services

Some of the content and functionality on our Sites may be provided by third parties that are not affiliated with us. For example, we enable you to share certain materials on our websites through social networking services, such as Facebook and Twitter. Third-party advertisers also may have a presence on some of our Sites. These third parties may collect or receive certain information about your use of our Sites, including through the use of cookies, web beacons, and Internet technologies, and this information may be collected over time and combined with information collected across different websites and online services.

Some of these companies participate in industry-developed programs designed to provide consumers choices about whether to receive targeted advertising. Please visit the websites operated by the Network Advertising Initiative (http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and Digital Advertising Alliance (http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more.

## Collection of Information From Children

We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of thirteen (13) online. If we learn that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with information, we will delete it in accordance with applicable law.

## Your Choices & Access to Your Information

**Choices.** Where permitted by law, we may send you offers or promotions. However, we give you choices about how we communicate with you. 

  * **Digital and Electronic Communications (including email and website):** If you no longer wish to continue receiving commercial emails from us or our business partners, you may follow the instructions contained in any such message. You may also contact us at privacy@arcadiapower.com for information about how to remove yourself from any of our mailing lists. 
  * **Postal mail:** If you would like to be removed from our postal mailing lists, please send an email to privacy@arcadiapower.com. Put the word “REMOVE” in the subject line. In the body of the email, please include your name and address and the database(s) from which you would like your information to be removed. 

Please note that, despite your opt-out selections, we may send you communications regarding transactions or services you have specifically requested or to inform you of important changes to our Sites, services, or policies. If you have multiple accounts, you may need to opt-out separately for each account in connection with the privacy choices described above.

**Access to Your Information.** The accuracy of your information is important to us. You can view or modify information stored with your user account by logging in to your account and accessing the https://login.arcadiapower.com 

## Your California Privacy Rights

California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of certain categories of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. We share Personal Information with third parties that provide services or products of interest to you for their direct marketing purposes.

## Information Security

We have in place various procedures to safeguard your information, including technical, administrative, and physical procedures intended to keep your information secure. However, please note that although we take reasonable steps to protect your information, no website, Internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure.

In addition, we take reasonable steps to ensure that we retain personal information about you only for so long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, or as required under any contract or by applicable law.

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact Arcadia Power, Inc. You may contact us by e-mail at privacy@arcadiapower.com. In addition, you may contact us at the following address:

Arcadia Power, Inc.

1789 Lanier Pl

Washington, DC 20009

## Changes to This Privacy Policy in the Future

Privacy laws and guidelines are part of a constantly changing environment. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. We recommend that you revisit this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current privacy practices. Your continued use of our Sites following any changes signifies your acceptance of these changes.

**Cookies, web beacons and other Internet technologies** We, as well as certain third parties that provide content and other functionality on our Sites, may use cookies, web beacons and other Internet technologies on our online Sites. This section provides you with more detail about these technologies. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file that may be stored on your computer or other device. They enable the entity that put the cookie on your device to recognize it across different websites, services, devices, and browsing sessions.

When you use a web browser to access our Sites, you may configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so click the “Help” menu of your browser to learn more about how to change your cookie preferences. The operating system of your device may contain additional controls for cookies. Please note that disabling cookies may affect your ability to access and use certain features of our Sites.

## Web Beacons

Web beacons and similar technologies are small bits of code, which are embedded in web pages, ads, and e-mail, that communicate with third parties. We may use web beacons, for example, to count the number of users who have visited a particular web page, to deliver or communicate with cookies, and to understand usage patterns. We also may include web beacons in e-mails to understand whether messages have been opened, acted on, or forwarded.

## Other Technologies

There are other local storage and Internet technologies, such as Local Shared Objects (also referred to as “Flash cookies”) and HTML5 local storage, that operate similarly to the cookies discussed above in that they are stored on your device and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences across different services and sessions. Please note that these technologies are distinct from cookies, and you may not be able to control them using standard browser tools and settings. For information about disabling or deleting information contained in Flash cookies, please click here.

## How We Use These Technologies

Our websites use these technologies for the following general purposes:

  * Administering and improving our websites, including helping us measure and research the effectiveness of our content, features, advertisements, and other communications. For example, we measure which pages and features website visitors are accessing and how much time they are spending on our web pages. We may include web beacons in e-mails, for example, to understand whether messages have been opened, acted on, or forwarded.
  * Storing your sign-in credentials and preferences so that you don’t have to enter those credentials and preferences each time you log on to a Site.
  * Helping us and third parties provide you with relevant content and advertising by collecting information about your use of our Sites and other websites.

Please see “How We Use Your Information” for details about how we use the information that we collect. By continuing to use the Arcadia Power websites and services, you consent to our use of cookies, web beacons, and other Internet technologies as described above.
